<situation name="ont" returnas="ont">
	<content>
		Ontological Layer
	</content>
	<relation name="ofType" returnas="ofType"/>
	<individual name="typeType" returnas="typeType" type="typeType">
		<content>
			Types
		</content>
		
	</individual>
	<situation name="rw" returnas="rw">
		<content>
			The World
		</content>
		<individual name="personType" type="typeType">
			<content>
				People
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="movieType" type="typeType">
			<content>
				Movies
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<relation name="performs">
			<content>
				<pseudo>
					<role role="performer"/>
					 performs <role role="performee"/>
					
				</pseudo>
				
			</content>
			
		</relation>
		<individual name="people.0000843" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Anne Bancroft" thumbnail="nm0000843">
					<bio>
						&lt;p&gt;Anna Maria Italiano was born 1931 in the Bronx, New York. She made her cinema &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/SearchBios?debut&quot;&gt;debut&lt;/a&gt; in 1952 in &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0044557/&quot;&gt;Don't Bother to Knock&lt;/a&gt; (1952). In the fifties she made a lot of movies as a supporting actress until she became a star with &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0056241/&quot;&gt;The Miracle Worker&lt;/a&gt; (1962), directed by &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0671957/&quot;&gt;Arthur Penn&lt;/a&gt;, for which she won an Academy &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/SearchBios?Award&quot;&gt;Award&lt;/a&gt;. The sixties in general were her best years: &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0058500/&quot;&gt;The Pumpkin Eater&lt;/a&gt; (1964) directed by &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0002338/&quot;&gt;Jack Clayton&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0060050/&quot;&gt;7 Women&lt;/a&gt; (1966) directed by &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0000406/&quot;&gt;John Ford&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0061722/&quot;&gt;The Graduate&lt;/a&gt; (1967) directed by &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0001566/&quot;&gt;Mike Nichols&lt;/a&gt;. In 1964 she married &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0000316/&quot;&gt;Mel Brooks&lt;/a&gt;. After the sixties she reduced her appearances in movies but still had some important roles like, for example, &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0087313/&quot;&gt;Garbo Talks&lt;/a&gt; (1984) directed by &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0001486/&quot;&gt;Sidney Lumet&lt;/a&gt;. She also began to make some TV films.&lt;/p&gt;
					</bio>
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0000163" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Dustin Hoffman" thumbnail="nm0000163">
					<bio>
						&lt;p&gt;Graduated from Los Angeles High School in 1955. Went to Santa Monica City College where he dropped out after a year due to bad grades. But before he did, he took an acting course because he was told that &quot;nobody flunks acting.&quot; Also received some training at Los Angeles Conservatory of Music. Decided to go into acting because he did not want to work or go into the service. Trained at The Pasadena Playhouse for two years.&lt;/p&gt;
					</bio>
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0001684" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Katharine Ross" thumbnail="nm0001684">
					<bio />
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0200122" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="William Daniels" thumbnail="noperson">
					<bio />
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0358069" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Murray Hamilton" thumbnail="noperson">
					<bio />
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0933361" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Elizabeth Wilson" thumbnail="noperson">
					<bio />
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0377750" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Buck Henry" thumbnail="noperson">
					<bio />
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0043011" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Brian Avery" thumbnail="nm0043011">
					<bio />
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0111754" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Walter Brooke" thumbnail="noperson">
					<bio />
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0001205" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Norman Fell" thumbnail="noperson">
					<bio>
						&lt;p&gt;Norman Fell was born in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania in 1924. He graduated from Temple University with a bachelor's degree in drama. During World War II, he was an Air Force tail gunner in the Pacific. After the war, he studied acting and obtained small parts in television and on stage. His first regular TV appearance was in the comedy series &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0048877/&quot;&gt;&amp;#34;Joe &amp;#38; Mabel&amp;#34;&lt;/a&gt; (1956). His best known TV role was that of Stanley Roper, the landlord in the very popular &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0075596/&quot;&gt;&amp;#34;Three's Company&amp;#34;&lt;/a&gt; (1977), which &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/SearchBios?debut&quot;&gt;debut&lt;/a&gt;ed in 1977, and its short lived spin-off, &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0078679/&quot;&gt;&amp;#34;The Ropers&amp;#34;&lt;/a&gt; (1979).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norman Fell died at the Motion Picture and Television Fund's retirement home in Woodland Hills CA, aged 74, survived by two daughters.&lt;/p&gt;
					</bio>
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0315933" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Alice Ghostley" thumbnail="noperson">
					<bio>
						&lt;p&gt;Whether portraying a withering wallflower, a drab and dowdy housewife, a klutzy maid or a cynical gossip, eccentric character comedienne Alice Ghostley had the ability to draw laughs from the skimpiest of material with a simple fret or whine. Making a name for herself on the Tony-winning &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/SearchBios?Broadway&quot;&gt;Broadway&lt;/a&gt; stage, her eternally forlorn looks later became an amusingly familiar plain-Jane presence on TV sitcoms and in an occasional film or two during the 50s, 60s and 70s.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alice was born in a whistle-stop railroad station in the tiny town of Eve, Missouri, where her father was employed as a telegraph operator. She grew up in various towns in the Midwest (Arkansas, Oklahoma) and began performing from the age of 5 where she was called upon to recite poetry, sing and tap-dance. Spurred on by a high school teacher, she studied drama at the University of Oklahoma but eventually left in order to pursue a career in New York with her sister Gladys.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Teaming together in an act called &quot;The Ghostley Sisters&quot;, Alice eventually went solo and developed her own cabaret show as a singer and comedienne, she toiled as a secretary to a music teacher in exchange for singing lessons, worked as a theater usherette in order to see free stage shows, paid her dues as a waitress, worked once for a detective agency, and even had a stint as a patch tester for a detergent company. No glamourpuss by any stretch of the imagination, she built her reputation as a singing funny lady.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The short-statured, auburn-haired entertainer received her star-making break singing the satirical ditty &quot;The Boston Beguine&quot; in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/SearchBios?Broadway&quot;&gt;Broadway&lt;/a&gt; stage revue &quot;New Faces of 1952&quot;, which also showcased up-and-coming stars &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0457755/&quot;&gt;Eartha Kitt&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0492655/&quot;&gt;Carol Lawrence&lt;/a&gt;, Hogan's Heroes co-star &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0165145/&quot;&gt;Robert Clary&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0001489/&quot;&gt;Paul Lynde&lt;/a&gt; to whom she would be invariably compared to what with their similar comic approach, fretful demeanors and dry sarcasm. The film version of &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0044963/&quot;&gt;New Faces&lt;/a&gt; (1954)_ featured pretty much the same cast. She and &quot;male counterpart&quot; Lynde would appear together in the same films and/or TV shows over the years.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With this momentum started, she continued on &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/SearchBios?Broadway&quot;&gt;Broadway&lt;/a&gt; with the short-lived musicals &quot;Sandhog&quot; (1954) featuring &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0144197/&quot;&gt;Jack Cassidy&lt;/a&gt;, &quot;Trouble in Tahiti&quot; (1955), &quot;Shangri-La&quot; (1956), again starring &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0144197/&quot;&gt;Jack Cassidy&lt;/a&gt;, and the legit comedy &quot;Maybe Tuesday&quot; (1958). A reliable sketch artist, she fared much better on stage in the 1960s playing a number of different characterizations in both &quot;A Thurber Carnival&quot; (1960), and opposite &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0481618/&quot;&gt;Bert Lahr&lt;/a&gt; in &quot;The Beauty Part&quot; (1962), for which she received a Tony nomination. She finally nabbed the Tony trophy as &quot;featured actress&quot; for her wonderful work as Mavis in the comedy play &quot;The Sign in Sidney Brustein's Window&quot; (1965).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By this time Alice had established herself on TV. She and good friend &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0050639/&quot;&gt;Kaye Ballard&lt;/a&gt; stole much of the proceedings as the evil stepsisters in the classic &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0000267/&quot;&gt;Julie Andrews&lt;/a&gt; version of &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0129672/&quot;&gt;Cinderella&lt;/a&gt; (1957) (TV), and she also recreated her &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/SearchBios?Broadway&quot;&gt;Broadway&lt;/a&gt; role in a small screen adaptation of _Shangri-La (1960) (TV)_. Although it was mighty hard to take away her comedy instincts, she did appear in a TV production of &quot;Twelfth Night&quot; as Maria opposite &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0263052/&quot;&gt;Maurice Evans&lt;/a&gt;' Malvolio, and graced such dramatic programs as &quot;Perry Mason&quot; and &quot;Naked City&quot;, as well as the film &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0056592/&quot;&gt;To Kill a Mockingbird&lt;/a&gt; (1962). She kept herself in the TV limelight as a frequent panelist on such game shows as &quot;The Hollywood Squares&quot; and &quot;The Match Game&quot;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enjoying a number of featured caricature roles in such lightweight comedies as &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0057341/&quot;&gt;My Six Loves&lt;/a&gt; (1963) with &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0001666/&quot;&gt;Debbie Reynolds&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0063821/&quot;&gt;With Six You Get Eggroll&lt;/a&gt; (1968) starring &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0000013/&quot;&gt;Doris Day&lt;/a&gt;, and the &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0001672/&quot;&gt;Joan Rivers&lt;/a&gt; starrer &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0078133/&quot;&gt;Rabbit Test&lt;/a&gt; (1978), she also had a small teacher role in the popular film version of &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0077631/&quot;&gt;Grease&lt;/a&gt; (1978). Alice primarily situated herself, however, on the sitcom circuit and appeared in a number of recurring 'nervous Nellie&quot; roles, topping it off as the painfully shy, dematerializing and accident-prone witch nanny Esmeralda in &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0057733/&quot;&gt;&amp;#34;Bewitched&amp;#34;&lt;/a&gt; (1964) from 1969-1972 (replacing the late &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0521079/&quot;&gt;Marion Lorne&lt;/a&gt;, who had played bumbling Aunt Clara), and as the batty friend Bernice in &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0090418/&quot;&gt;&amp;#34;Designing Women&amp;#34;&lt;/a&gt; (1986).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 1978 Alice replaced &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0521702/&quot;&gt;Dorothy Loudon&lt;/a&gt; as cruel Miss Hannigan in &quot;Annie&quot;, her last &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/SearchBios?Broadway&quot;&gt;Broadway&lt;/a&gt; stand. Alice would play the mean-spirited scene-stealer on and off for nearly a decade in various parts of the country. Other musicals during this time included &quot;Take Me Along&quot;, &quot;Bye, Bye Birdie&quot; (as the overbearing mother), and the raucous revue &quot;Nunsense&quot;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A series of multiple strokes ended her career come the millennium and she passed away of colon cancer on September 21, 2007. Her long-time husband of fifty years, Italian comedic actor &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0649939/&quot;&gt;Felice Orlandi&lt;/a&gt; died in 2003. The couple had no children.&lt;/p&gt;
					</bio>
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0521079" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Marion Lorne" thumbnail="noperson">
					<bio>
						&lt;p&gt;Forever embraced as the dithering, bumbling Aunt Clara on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0057733/&quot;&gt;&amp;#34;Bewitched&amp;#34;&lt;/a&gt; (1964) television series, endearing character actress Marion Lorne had a five-decade-long career on the stage before she became a household name. Born Marion Lorne MacDougall, she grew up in her native Pennsylvania, the daughter of Scottish and English immigrants. Trained at the American Academy of Dramatic Arts in New York, she appeared in stock shows, and was on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/SearchBios?Broadway&quot;&gt;Broadway&lt;/a&gt; boards by 1905. She married playwright &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0352506/&quot;&gt;Walter C. Hackett&lt;/a&gt; and performed in many of his plays throughout the 1920s and 1930s. They eventually settled in England where they founded the Whitehall Theater. It was there that Marion began to patent her comedy eccentrics. Upon Hackett's death in 1944, she returned to the States and became a hit in such tailor-made stage shows as &quot;Harvey&quot;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marion made a definitive impression in her movie &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/SearchBios?debut&quot;&gt;debut&lt;/a&gt; at age 60+ with &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0000033/&quot;&gt;Alfred Hitchcock&lt;/a&gt;'s immortal suspenser &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0044079/&quot;&gt;Strangers on a Train&lt;/a&gt; (1951) as murderer &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0908153/&quot;&gt;Robert Walker&lt;/a&gt;'s smothering mother. Unfortunately, Hollywood movies used her only a couple of times after that -- a grievously sad waste of a talented comedienne. Marion quickly turned to TV and became a ditsy hit in such sitcoms as _&quot;Mister Peepers&quot; (1952)_ and &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0050059/&quot;&gt;&amp;#34;Sally&amp;#34;&lt;/a&gt; (1957), gaining quirky comedy status as well on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0051276/&quot;&gt;&amp;#34;The Garry Moore Show&amp;#34;&lt;/a&gt; (1958). However, it was her role as the befuddled, amusingly perplexed witch-aunt on &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0057733/&quot;&gt;&amp;#34;Bewitched&amp;#34;&lt;/a&gt; (1964) -- whether bouncing into walls or conjuring up some unintended piece of witchcraft -- which put a lasting sheen on her long career. She deservedly was rewarded with an Emmy trophy for &quot;Best Supporting Actress &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/SearchBios?Award&quot;&gt;Award&lt;/a&gt;,&quot; albeit posthumously. Sadly, Marion succumbed to a heart attack ten days before the actual ceremony in 1968. The star of the series, &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0000548/&quot;&gt;Elizabeth Montgomery&lt;/a&gt;, accepted the &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/SearchBios?award&quot;&gt;award&lt;/a&gt; on her behalf.&lt;/p&gt;
					</bio>
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0301841" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Eddra Gale" thumbnail="noperson">
					<bio />
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0234975" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Buddy Douglas" thumbnail="noperson">
					<bio />
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0000377" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Richard Dreyfuss" thumbnail="nm0000377">
					<bio>
						&lt;p&gt;American leading man who has played his fair share of irritating pests and brash, ambitious hustlers, Dreyfuss worked his way up through bit parts (&lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0061722/&quot;&gt;The Graduate&lt;/a&gt; (1967), for one) and TV before gaining attention with his portrayal of Baby Face Nelson in &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0587518/&quot;&gt;John Milius&lt;/a&gt;' &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0069976/&quot;&gt;Dillinger&lt;/a&gt; (1973). He gained prominence as a college-bound young man in &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0069704/&quot;&gt;American Graffiti&lt;/a&gt; (1973) and as a nervy Jewish kid with high hopes in &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0071155/&quot;&gt;The Apprenticeship of Duddy Kravitz&lt;/a&gt; (1974). By the latter part of the 1970s, Dreyfuss was established as a major star, playing leads (and alter-egos) for 'Steven Spielberg' in two of the top-grossing films of the that decade: &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0073195/&quot;&gt;Jaws&lt;/a&gt; (1975) and &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0075860/&quot;&gt;Close Encounters of the Third Kind&lt;/a&gt; (1977). He won a Best Actor Oscar in his first romantic lead as an out-of-work actor in &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0076095/&quot;&gt;The Goodbye Girl&lt;/a&gt; (1977). Dreyfuss also produced and starred in the entertaining private eye movie &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0077233/&quot;&gt;The Big Fix&lt;/a&gt; (1978). After a brief lull in the early 1980s, a well-publicized drug problem and a succession of commercial disappointments (&lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0080556/&quot;&gt;The Competition&lt;/a&gt; (1980), &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0083326/&quot;&gt;Whose Life Is It Anyway?&lt;/a&gt; (1981), &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0087006/&quot;&gt;The Buddy System&lt;/a&gt; (1984)), a clean and sober Dreyfuss re-established himself in the mid-'as one of Hollywood's more engaging leads. He co-starred with &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0000541/&quot;&gt;Bette Midler&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0000560/&quot;&gt;Nick Nolte&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0005196/&quot;&gt;Paul Mazursky&lt;/a&gt;'s popular &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0090966/&quot;&gt;Down and Out in Beverly Hills&lt;/a&gt; (1986). That same year Dreyfuss provided the narration and appeared in the opening and closing &quot;bookends&quot; of &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0001661/&quot;&gt;Rob Reiner&lt;/a&gt;'s nostalgic &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0092005/&quot;&gt;Stand by Me&lt;/a&gt; (1986). He quickly followed up with &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0093660/&quot;&gt;Nuts&lt;/a&gt; (1987) opposite &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0000659/&quot;&gt;Barbra Streisand&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0001469/&quot;&gt;Barry Levinson&lt;/a&gt;'s &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0094155/&quot;&gt;Tin Men&lt;/a&gt; (1987) with &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0000362/&quot;&gt;Danny DeVito&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0094025/&quot;&gt;Stakeout&lt;/a&gt; (1987) with &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0000389/&quot;&gt;Emilio Estevez&lt;/a&gt;. Dreyfuss continued working steadily through the end of the 1980s and into the 1990s, most notably in Mazursky's &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0095654/&quot;&gt;Moon Over Parador&lt;/a&gt; (1988), Spielberg's &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0096794/&quot;&gt;Always&lt;/a&gt; (1989), &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0100395/&quot;&gt;Postcards from the Edge&lt;/a&gt; (1990) and &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0100519/&quot;&gt;Rosencrantz &amp;#38; Guildenstern Are Dead&lt;/a&gt; (1990). He appeared as a member of an ensemble that included &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0000456/&quot;&gt;Holly Hunter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0001687/&quot;&gt;Gena Rowlands&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0000732/&quot;&gt;Danny Aiello&lt;/a&gt; in the romantic comedy _Once Around_ (1991)- and opposite &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0000195/&quot;&gt;Bill Murray&lt;/a&gt; in the successful comedy &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0103241/&quot;&gt;What About Bob?&lt;/a&gt; (1991). Dreyfuss has also remained active in the theater (Death And The Maiden 1992) and on TV. He returned to features in the adaptation of &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0800319/&quot;&gt;Neil Simon&lt;/a&gt;'s play &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0107443/&quot;&gt;Lost in Yonkers&lt;/a&gt; (1993) and followed with a supporting turn as the querulous political opponent in &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0112346/&quot;&gt;The American President&lt;/a&gt; (1995). Dreyfuss received some of the best notices of his career as a determined, inspiring music teacher coping with a deaf son and the demands of his career in &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0113862/&quot;&gt;Mr. Holland's Opus&lt;/a&gt; (1995).&lt;/p&gt;
					</bio>
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0268286" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Mike Farrell" thumbnail="nm0268286">
					<bio>
						&lt;p&gt;Mike is one of four children. His father, Joe, who died in 1956, was a carpenter at Hollywood studios. Mike attended grammar school with &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0000081/&quot;&gt;Natalie Wood&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0625699/&quot;&gt;Ricky Nelson&lt;/a&gt;. He entered the marines in the 1950's for two years. Later, he attended the University of California at Los Angeles and studied acting at the &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0179786/&quot;&gt;Jeff Corey&lt;/a&gt; Workshop. He started getting big parts in movies, which led to a regular role on &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0058796/&quot;&gt;&amp;#34;Days of Our Lives&amp;#34;&lt;/a&gt; (1965) and, ultimately, to &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0068098/&quot;&gt;&amp;#34;M*A*S*H&amp;#34;&lt;/a&gt; (1972). When &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0068098/&quot;&gt;&amp;#34;M*A*S*H&amp;#34;&lt;/a&gt; (1972) went off the air, he resisted series TV for many years until he was offered &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0177991/&quot;&gt;&amp;#34;Providence&amp;#34;&lt;/a&gt; (1999). In the meantime, he formed his own production company, which made the &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0000245/&quot;&gt;Robin Williams&lt;/a&gt; vehicle, &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0129290/&quot;&gt;Patch Adams&lt;/a&gt; (1998), based on Mike's own acquaintance with the doctor. Mike is very politically involved. He lobbied against the firing of gay teachers. He was outspoken about the US involvement in Ecuador in the 80s. He served as a member of California's Commission on Judicial Performance from February 2, 1998 to February 28, 2001.&lt;/p&gt;
					</bio>
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0292116" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Elisabeth Fraser" thumbnail="noperson">
					<bio />
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0323304" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Donald F. Glut" thumbnail="noperson">
					<bio />
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0390118" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Harry Holcombe" thumbnail="noperson">
					<bio />
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0390418" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Jonathan Hole" thumbnail="noperson">
					<bio />
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0588771" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Lainie Miller" thumbnail="noperson">
					<bio />
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0614101" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Ben Murphy" thumbnail="nm0614101">
					<bio />
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0685736" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Noam Pitlik" thumbnail="noperson">
					<bio />
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<individual name="people.0001798" type="personType">
			<content>
				<information name="Kevin Tighe" thumbnail="noperson">
					<bio>
						&lt;p&gt;This beefy, genial-looking character actor was born John Kevin Fishburn in Los Angeles. Performing as a child from age 10, Tighe initially attended Pasadena City College. He later obtained a Masters Degree in Theater, then taught drama at USC. Living Bohemian-style out of a suitcase after he decided to pursue acting professionally, he was in the United Kingdom trying to obtain work at various prestigious theater companies when producer &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0916131/&quot;&gt;Jack Webb&lt;/a&gt; acquired his services for the &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0068067/&quot;&gt;&amp;#34;Emergency!&amp;#34;&lt;/a&gt; (1972) medical series alongside &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0298333/&quot;&gt;Robert Fuller&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0518728/&quot;&gt;Julie London&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0873757/&quot;&gt;Bobby Troup&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0544168/&quot;&gt;Randolph Mantooth&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tighe gained moderate TV stardom as paramedic Roy DeSoto and the series lasted a financially lucrative five years. Along with that came a spin-off animated series and some follow-up TV-movies. He returned to acting study in order to refresh his skills during the slow &quot;post-Emergency&quot; period and managed to work with such inspiring notables as &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm0012245/&quot;&gt;Stella Adler&lt;/a&gt;. His perseverance paid off with a steady stream of gray-haired character roles starting in the 80s -- predominantly in rugged fare. Although he made his &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/SearchBios?Broadway&quot;&gt;Broadway&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/SearchBios?debut&quot;&gt;debut&lt;/a&gt; with &quot;Open Admissions&quot; in 1984, the show folded after only a couple of weeks. On film, however, Kevin did quite well by appearing in such high-profile movies as &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0093509/&quot;&gt;Matewan&lt;/a&gt; (1987), where he first played a &quot;bad guy,&quot; &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0095082/&quot;&gt;Eight Men Out&lt;/a&gt; (1988), &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0098206/&quot;&gt;Road House&lt;/a&gt; (1989), &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0099044/&quot;&gt;Another 48 Hrs.&lt;/a&gt; (1990), &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0101588/&quot;&gt;City of Hope&lt;/a&gt; (1991), &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0104990/&quot;&gt;Newsies&lt;/a&gt; (1992), &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0108550/&quot;&gt;What's Eating Gilbert Grape&lt;/a&gt; (1993), &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0113451/&quot;&gt;Jade&lt;/a&gt; (1995) and &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0140397/&quot;&gt;Mumford&lt;/a&gt; (1999).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On TV he has had a number of prime support rules over the years playing everything from Thomas Jefferson and William Randolph Hearst to the Kansas patriarch who was senselessly slaughtered along with his family by the &quot;In Cold Blood&quot; killers. Known for his serious-minded roles, Kevin has tackled a number of generals, attorneys, governors, doctors, coaches, even psychics during his long career. He won the Canadian &quot;Genie&quot; &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/SearchBios?Award&quot;&gt;Award&lt;/a&gt; for his supporting role in &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/title/tt0107179/&quot;&gt;I Love a Man in Uniform&lt;/a&gt; (1993). His only child, &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/name/nm1635226/&quot;&gt;Jennifer Tighe&lt;/a&gt;, is also an actress.&lt;/p&gt;
					</bio>
					
				</information>
				
			</content>
			
		</individual>
		<situation name="movies.0061722" type="movieType">
			<content>
				<title>
					The Graduate
				</title>
				<releaseDate>
					1999-11-30
				</releaseDate>
				<tagline>
					The Movie That Became A Legend [Video Australia]
				</tagline>
				<plot>
					 Ben has recently graduated college, with his parents now expecting great things from him. At his &quot;Homecoming&quot; party, Mrs. Robinson, the wife of his father's business partner, has Ben drive her home, which leads to an affair between the two. The affair eventually ends, but comes back to haunt him when he finds himself falling for Elaine, Mrs. Robinson's daughter. &lt;i&gt;  Written by  &lt;a href=&quot;http://akas.imdb.com/SearchPlotWriters/?Zac%20Abrams&quot;&gt;Zac Abrams&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/i&gt;  
				</plot>
				
			</content>
			<individual name="characters.Mrs. Robinson" type="personType">
				<content>
					Mrs. Robinson
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Ben Braddock" type="personType">
				<content>
					Ben Braddock
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Elaine Robinson" type="personType">
				<content>
					Elaine Robinson
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Mr. Braddock" type="personType">
				<content>
					Mr. Braddock
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Mr. Robinson" type="personType">
				<content>
					Mr. Robinson
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Mrs. Braddock" type="personType">
				<content>
					Mrs. Braddock
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Room Clerk" type="personType">
				<content>
					Room Clerk
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Carl Smith" type="personType">
				<content>
					Carl Smith
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Mr. McGuire" type="personType">
				<content>
					Mr. McGuire
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Mr. McCleery" type="personType">
				<content>
					Mr. McCleery
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Mrs. Singleman" type="personType">
				<content>
					Mrs. Singleman
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Miss DeWitte" type="personType">
				<content>
					Miss DeWitte
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Woman on Bus" type="personType">
				<content>
					Woman on Bus
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Bellhop in Hotel Lobby (uncredited)" type="personType">
				<content>
					Bellhop in Hotel Lobby (uncredited)
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Boarding House Resident (uncredited)" type="personType">
				<content>
					Boarding House Resident (uncredited)
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Bellhop in Hotel Lobby (uncredited)" type="personType">
				<content>
					Bellhop in Hotel Lobby (uncredited)
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Second Lady (uncredited)" type="personType">
				<content>
					Second Lady (uncredited)
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.College student (uncredited)" type="personType">
				<content>
					College student (uncredited)
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.The Minister (uncredited)" type="personType">
				<content>
					The Minister (uncredited)
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Mr. Singleman (uncredited)" type="personType">
				<content>
					Mr. Singleman (uncredited)
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Night Club Stripper (uncredited)" type="personType">
				<content>
					Night Club Stripper (uncredited)
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Shaving Student (uncredited)" type="personType">
				<content>
					Shaving Student (uncredited)
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Gas Station Attendant (uncredited)" type="personType">
				<content>
					Gas Station Attendant (uncredited)
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			<individual name="characters.Extra (uncredited)" type="personType">
				<content>
					Extra (uncredited)
				</content>
				
			</individual>
			
		</situation>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0000843"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Mrs. Robinson"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0000163"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Ben Braddock"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0001684"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Elaine Robinson"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0200122"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Mr. Braddock"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0358069"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Mr. Robinson"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0933361"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Mrs. Braddock"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0377750"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Room Clerk"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0043011"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Carl Smith"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0111754"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Mr. McGuire"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0001205"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Mr. McCleery"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0315933"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Mrs. Singleman"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0521079"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Miss DeWitte"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0301841"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Woman on Bus"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0234975"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Bellhop in Hotel Lobby (uncredited)"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0000377"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Boarding House Resident (uncredited)"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0268286"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Bellhop in Hotel Lobby (uncredited)"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0292116"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Second Lady (uncredited)"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0323304"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.College student (uncredited)"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0390118"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.The Minister (uncredited)"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0390418"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Mr. Singleman (uncredited)"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0588771"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Night Club Stripper (uncredited)"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0614101"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Shaving Student (uncredited)"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0685736"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Gas Station Attendant (uncredited)"/>
			
		</infon>
		<infon relation="performs">
			<arc role="performer" arg="people.0001798"/>
			<arc role="performee" arg="characters.Extra (uncredited)"/>
			
		</infon>
		
	</situation>
	
</situation>
